Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Administrative Records, 1921-2010; 486757
  - Building Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on Responsibility for Design and Installation of Building Construction, 1957; 487092 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Building Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on Responsibility for Design and Installation of Building Construction, 1958; 487091 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Building Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on Responsibility on Construction Jobs, 1957; 487090 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Building Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on Responsibility on Construction Jobs, 1958; 487089 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Building Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on Retained Percentages, 1955-1958; 487088 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Building Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on Shop and Installation Drawings, 1955-1956, 1966; 487087 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Building Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on Temporary Heat, Light, and Power, 1955; 487086 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Building Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on Test Boring Information, 1960-1965; 487085 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Building Trades Agreements and Expiration Dates, 1978; 487084 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Business/Labor Coalition for New York, 1983; 487083 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Certificate of Incorporation: New York Building Congress, 1937; 487082 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - City Planning and Development Committee, 1991; 487081 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Clark, Bradford N. (President), 1958-1962; 487080 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Clark, Bradford N. (Public Relations Committee), 1981-1982; 487079 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Coletti, Louis J. (President): Proposals, Statements, and Testimony, 1986-1991; 487078 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Collins, John J. (President; Chairman, Council of Presidents), 1969-1986; 487077 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Building Conditions, 1923-1927; 487076 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Codes: "Code of Ethics," drafts, 1921; 487075 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Codes: "Code of Ethics," pamphlets, 1921; 487074 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Cost-Plus-a-Fixed-Fee and Other Types of Construction Contracts, 1945; 487073 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Disposal of Construction Wastes, 1958; 487072 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1932; 487071 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Old Age Pensions and Insurance: Pension Study, 1932; 487070 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Relationship between General and Subcontractors, 1949-1950; 487069 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Reorganization of the New York City Housing Authority, 1958; 487068 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Revision of Contract between General and Subcontractor, 1960; 487067 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Trends toward Independent Subcontracts, 1951; 487066 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Trends toward Independent Subcontracts, 1952; 487065 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Trends toward Independent Subcontracts, 1954; 487064 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Committees: Lists, 1934-2007, undated; 487063 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Communication and Membership Committee: Agendas, 2002-2007; 487062 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Communications Committee, 2010; 487061 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, circa 1945; 487060 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1956; 487059 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1978; 487058 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1986; 487057 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1987, 1989; 487056 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1991-1992; 487055 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1995; 487054 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1962; 487053 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1978; 487052 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1986-1987; 487051 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Construction Controls Committee, 1951; 487050 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Construction Industry Advancement Program, 1994-1995; 487049 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Construction Industry Advisory Committee, 1976, 2009; 487048 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Construction Industry Development Board, 1995-1996; 487047 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Construction Industry Development Board: Construction Environmental Task Force, 1982-1986; 487046 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Construction Industry Development Board: Contract with New York Task Force, 1996; 487045 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Construction Industry Development Board: Creating and Industry Database Task Force, 1996; 487044 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Construction Industry Practices Committee, 1977; 487043 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Construction Industry Practices Committee: Recommendations, 1982-1983; 487042 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Construction Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on "Or Equal" Clause, 1977; 487041 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Council of Business and Labor, 1984-1988; 487040 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Council of Business and Labor, 1989-1990; 487039 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Council of Presidents, 1975-1976; 487038 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Council of Presidents, 1977; 487037 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Council of Presidents, 1978; 487036 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1979; 487035 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1979; 487034 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Aug 1980; 487033 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Council of Presidents, Sep-Dec 1980; 487032 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-May 1981; 487031 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Council of Presidents, Jun-Dec 1981; 487030 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Council of Presidents, 1982; 487029 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Mar 1983; 487028 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Council of Presidents, Apr-Jun 1983; 487027 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Sep 1983; 487026 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Council of Presidents, Oct-Dec 1983; 487025 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1984; 487024 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1984; 487023 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1985; 487022 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1985; 487021 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1986; 487020 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1986; 487019 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1987; 487018 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1987; 487017 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Council of Presidents, 1988; 487016 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Council of Presidents, 1989-1990; 487015 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Council of Presidents, 1991; 487014 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Council of Presidents, 1992; 487013 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Council of Presidents, 1993; 487012 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Council of Presidents, 1994; 487011 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Council of Presidents, 1995; 487010 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Council of Presidents, 1996; 487009 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Council of Presidents, 2005; 487008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Council of Presidents, 2007-2008; 487007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Council of Presidents, Undated; 487006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Council of Presidents: Agendas, 2000-2007; 487005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Council of Presidents: Finances, 1979-1982; 487004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Council of Presidents: Finances, 1987-1989; 487003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Council of Presidents: Host Schedules, 1985-1991; 487002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Council of Presidents: Legislative Luncheon, 1979; 487001 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Council of Presidents: Luncheons, 1989; 487000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Council of Presidents: Nominating Committee, 1982-1985; 486999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Council of Presidents: Nominations, 1988; 486998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Council of Presidents: Reorganization, 1977-1978; 486997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Council of Presidents: Roster, Undated; 486996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Council of Presidents: Westway Support Campaign, 1981-1986; 486995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Craftsmanship: Certificate of Superior Craftsmanship, circa 1920s; 486994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Craftsmanship: Committee on Recognition of Craftsmanship, 1925; 486993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Craftsmanship: Committee on Recognition of Craftsmanship, circa 1920s; 486992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Craftsmanship: General, circa 1920s; 486991 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Craftsmanship: "How it is Put into Effect", 1926; 486990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Craftsmanship: Recognition in "Building Age", 1927; 486989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Craftsmanship: "Recognition of Craftsmanship", 1925, 1929; 486988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Craftsmanship: "What is a Good Craftsman?", circa 1920s; 486987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cutler, Robert W. (President), 1964-1969; 486986 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dues Policy Committee, 1987; 486985 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Economic Development Committee, 1995; 486984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Economic Development Committee, 1996; 486983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Economic Development Committee, 1999-2000; 486982 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Economic Development Committee, 2004-2006; 486981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Economic Development Committee, 2007-2008; 486980 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Economic Development Committee: Agendas, 2000-2007; 486979 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Economic Impact Steering Committee, 1990; 486978 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Edifice: Background, 1977-1978; 486977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Education Committee, 1974; 486976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Education Committee, 1979; 486975 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Education Committee, 1994-1996; 486974 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Education and Healthcare Committee, 1994; 486973 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Educational Facilities Construction Task Force (Ed Con), 1987-1989; 486972 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Energy Committee (I), 1994; 486971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Energy Committee (II), 1994; 486970 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Energy Committee, 1995; 486969 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Energy Committee, 1996; 486968 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Energy Committee, 2004-2006; 486967 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Energy Committee, 2007-2010; 486966 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Energy Committee: Agendas, 2000-2007; 486965 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Environmental Committee, 2002-2007; 486964 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Environmental Committee: Brownfields Subcommittee, 2001; 486963 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Environmental Task Force, 1982-1986; 486962 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Escalation and Shortages Committee, 1974; 486961 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Executive Committee, 1925; 486960 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-1987; 486959 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Executive Committee, 1988; 486958 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Executive Committee, 1989; 486957 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Executive Committee, 1990; 486956 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Executive Committee, 1991; 486955 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Executive Committee, 1992; 486954 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Executive Committee, 1993; 486953 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1994; 486952 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Executive Committee, 1995; 486951 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Executive Committee, 1996; 486950 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Executive Committee, 1999-2000; 486949 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Executive Committee, 2001; 486948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, 2002; 486947 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 2005; 486946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, 2007; 486945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 2008; 486944 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, 2010; 486943 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, Undated; 486942 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee: Agendas, 2000-2007; 486941 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fact Finding Committee, 1930-1931; 486940 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Finances, 1927; 486939 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Finances, 1934-1940; 486938 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Finances, 1962; 486937 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Finances, 1978-1984; 486936 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Finances, 1986; 486935 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Finances, 1987; 486934 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Finances, 1988; 486933 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Finances, 1989; 486932 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Finances, 1990-1991; 486931 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Finances, 1992-1993; 486930 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Finances, 1994-1996; 486929 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Finances, 2007, Undated; 486928 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Finances: Business Expansion Plan, 1988-1989; 486927 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Finances: Ledger, Burt L. Fenner Memorial Fund, 1926-1959; 486926 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Finances: Ledger, General, 1944-1963; 486925 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Finances: Ledger, General, 1963-1974; 486924 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Finances: Ledger, Luncheons & Outings, 1975-1976; 486923 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Financial Reports, 1998, 2007; 486922 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Financial Statements, 1988, 1995; 486921 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fire Safety Committee, 1971; 486920 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Future of the Construction Industry Committee, 1971; 486919 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Future of the Construction Industry Committee, 1973; 486918 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee, 1974; 486917 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee, 1976-1983; 486916 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee: New York City Charter Revision, 1975-1988; 486915 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Governor's Advisory Committee on the New York City Construction Industry, 1988; 486914 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Haines, Charles (President), 1962-1972; 486913 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Harris, Michael M. (President), 1972-1976; 486912 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Healthcare Committee, 1994-1996; 486911 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Healthcare Committee, 2010; 486910 (Box 6, Folder 38a)
  - Hennessey, John F. (President), 1957-1973; 486909 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Housing Committee, 1981; 486908 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Housing Committee, 1986; 486907 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Insurance and Bonding Committee, 1980; 486906 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Joint Building Industry Committee on City Contracts, 1952-1955; 486905 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Joint Energy Committee (Real Estate Board of New York, NYBC, & Association for a Better New York), 1980-1983; 486904 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Land Use Review Committee, 1989; 486903 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Land Utilization Committee: Land Usage, 1936; 486902 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Land Utilization Committee: Problems Affecting Housing, 1938; 486901 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Land Utilization Committee: Research Bulletins, 1933-1934; 486900 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Legislative Committee, 1960-1970; 486899 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Committee, 1973, 1977-1979; 486898 (Box 7, Folder 1a)
  - Legislative Committee, 1980; 486897 (Box 7, Folder 1b)
  - Legislative Committee, 1981; 486896 (Box 7, Folder 1c)
  - Legislative Committee, 1982-1983; 486895 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Committee, 1984-1986; 486894 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Report, 1978-1982; 486893 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Report, 1983-1988; 486892 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Liasion Committee, 1987; 486891 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Liasion Councils, 1987; 486890 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Management Committee, 2010; 486889 (Box 7, Folder 7a)
  - Membership Applications, 1936, 1951, Undated; 486888 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Membership Committee, 1955-1958; 486887 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Membership Committee, 1976-1977; 486886 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Membership Committee, 1980-1981; 486885 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Membership Committee, 1983; 486884 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Membership Committee, 1986-1989; 486883 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Membership Committee, 1994-1995; 486882 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Membership Committee, 1996; 486881 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Membership Committee: Agendas, 2000-2001; 486880 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Membership Committee: Correspondence, 1995; 486879 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1924, 1978-1996; 486878 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Membership Expansion Campaign, 1924; 486877 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Membership: Invoices, 1995; 486876 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Life Members, 1962-1984; 486875 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Membership Lists (Yearbook), 1923-1924; 486874 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Membership Lists (Yearbook), 1925-1926; 486873 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Membership Lists (Yearbook), 1928-1929; 486872 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Membership Lists, 1931; 486871 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Membership Lists, 1945-1946; 486870 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Membership Lists, 1956-1957; 486869 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Membership Lists, 1968-1969; 486868 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Membership Lists, 1978-1980; 486867 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Membership Lists, 1994-1995, Undated; 486866 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Membership Lists: Officers, 1945, Undated; 486865 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Membership: New Members, 1982-1991; 486864 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Membership: New Members, 1994; 486863 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Membership: New Members, 1995; 486862 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Membership: New Members, 1996; 486861 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Membership: New Members, 1997; 486860 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Membership Packet, 2006; 486859 (Box 7, Folder 36a)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1955; 486858 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1983-1987; 486857 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1988; 486856 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1989; 486855 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1990-1991; 486854 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1994; 486853 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1995; 486852 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1996; 486851 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Membership Renewals, 1987-1991; 486850 (Box 8, Folder 1a)
  - Membership Renewals, 1994; 486849 (Box 8, Folder 1b)
  - Membership Renewals, Jan 1995; 486848 (Box 8, Folder 1c)
  - Membership Renewals, Feb 1995; 486847 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Membership Renewals, Mar 1995; 486846 (Box 8, Folder 2a)
  - Membership Renewals, Apr 1995; 486845 (Box 8, Folder 2b)
  - Membership Renewals, May 1995; 486844 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Membership Renewals, Jun 1995; 486843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Membership Renewals, Jul 1995; 486842 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Membership Renewals, Aug 1995; 486841 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Membership Renewals, Oct 1995; 486840 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Membership Renewals, Nov 1995; 486839 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Membership Renewals, 1996; 486838 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Membership Reports, 1978; 486837 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Membership Reports, 1988-1991; 486836 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Membership Reports, 1995; 486835 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Withdrawals and Lapsed, 1983-1991; 486834 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Withdrawals and Lapsed, 1996; 486833 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Memos, 1932; 486832 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Memos, 1954; 486831 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Memos, 1976-1978; 486830 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Memos, 1980-1985; 486829 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Memos, 1986-1989; 486828 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Memos, 1990-1994; 486827 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Memos, 1995-1996; 486826 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Memos, 2008, Undated; 486825 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Mentor Committee, 1988-1990; 486824 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority - Construction Industry Working Group, 2000-2006; 486823 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority - Construction Industry Working Group, 2008; 486822 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority - Construction Industry Working Group: Agendas, 2000-2007; 486821 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - New York Building Foundation: Annual Report, 2008; 486820 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - New York Building Foundation: Board of Governors, 2007-2008; 486819 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - New York Building Foundation: Board of Governors, 2010; 486818 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - New York Building Foundation: Board of Governors: Agendas, 2000-2007; 486817 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - New York Building Foundation: Board of Governors Membership Directory, 2009-2010; 486816 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - New York Building Foundation: Construction Site Improvement Project, 2008; 486815 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - New York Building Foundation: Construction Site Improvement Project: Sidewalk Sheds Committee, 2007-2008; 486814 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - New York Building Foundation: Executive Committee, 2007-2008; 486813 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Nominating Committee, 1977; 486812 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Nominating Committee, 1981-1986; 486811 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Nominating Committee, 1988-1991; 486810 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Nominating Committee, 1994-1995; 486809 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Nominating Committee, 1996; 486808 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Nominating Committee, 1997; 486807 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Nominating Committee, 1998; 486806 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Nominating Committee, 1999; 486805 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Nominating Committee, 2000; 486804 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Organization Chart (NYBC) [additional copy in oversize box 23], 1980-1981; 486803 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Personnel Policy Subcommittee, 1996; 486802 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Pictures of Past Presidents, Correspondence re:, 1955; 486801 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Policy Guidance: Response Sheets, 1989; 486800 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Policymaking Committee, 1987; 486799 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Procurement Policy Committee, 1995; 486798 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Program Committee, 1924; 486797 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Program Committee, 1977; 486796 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Program Committee, 1987-1988; 486795 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Public Agency Council, 1996; 486794 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Public Agency Council, 1999-2004; 486793 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Public Building Committee, 1999-2000; 486792 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Public Building Committee, 2004-2006; 486791 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Public Building Committee, 2007-2009; 486790 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Public Building Committee: Agendas, 2002-2007; 486789 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Public Construction Task Force, 1988-1989; 486788 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Public Procurement Committee, 1994; 486787 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Public Procurement Committee, 1996; 486786 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Public Procurement Committee, 2001-2008; 486785 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Public Procurement Committee: Agendas, 2003-2006; 486784 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1977; 486783 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1980-1981; 486782 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Public Relations: Wachsman Proposal, 1977; 486781 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Publication Committee, 1978; 486780 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Reorganization Committee, 1935; 486779 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Research Project Advisory Board, 1989; 486778 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Schaffner, Charles (President), 1970-1982; 486777 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Search Committee, 1993; 486776 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Seasonal Operations Committee: "Seasonal Employment in the Building Trades", 1922; 486775 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Seasonal Operations Committee: "Seasonal Employment in the Building Trades", 1930; 486774 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Special Committee on Hod Hoists and House Cars, 1926, Undated; 486773 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Standards Committee: Standard Specifications, 1929, 1939; 486772 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Strategic Planning Committee, 1988; 486771 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Task Force on Construction Costs, 2007; 486770 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Tight Money Committee, 1957; 486769 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Trans Hudson Express Tunnel Project, 2008; 486768 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 1992-1994; 486767 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 1995-1996; 486766 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 1999; 486765 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 2006-2007; 486764 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 2008; 486763 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, Undated; 486762 (Box 9, Folder 30)